betfot.com 2014-09-22

# Privacy Policy | betfoot.com

**Privacy Policy**

**Use of our Website**

By using this website, you agree to the Privacy Policy set out below. We will review this Privacy Policy periodically, and reserve the right to modify and update it at any time.

**Notification of Changes**  
Changes to the Privacy Policy will come into effect immediately upon notification on this Site.

Your continued use of this Site following notification will constitute your acceptance of these changes. We recommend you review this Privacy Policy periodically.

Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information, as your use of our service will indicate your acceptance of its content.

Betfoot collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our games and to make more games available to you in due course. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest prize information, winner's announcements, Jackpots, special offers, new games and other information we think you'd like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop new games.

You can choose whether to receive all or none of these communications when you complete the registration process. You can also update your personal contact preferences at any time when logged in in the casino/poker or betting application.

**How we collect personal information.**  
When you register with betfoot we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.

Like many websites, betfoot’ websites use "cookie" technology. When you first connect to one of our sites, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you, except your first name so we can welcome you on your next visit. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our sites so we can make the sites even better.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look in the help menu of your browser. In some of our emails to you, we use a "click-through URL". When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-troughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every betfoot employee.

**Betfoot** Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.

**Contact Details**  
If you have any queries or complaints relating to the handling of your personal information, please contact us at [support@betfoot.com](mailto:support@betfoot.com)
